# NAVAN KANG

# CONTACT

(650) 804 9722

navankang@gmail.com

## **OBJECTIVE**

Looking for a Customer Relationship, Account Management and/or Partner Management role within the Health, Environmental, Technology and Financial /Economic verticals. Over 6+ years of successful experience in building new customer relationships, along with establishing / growing stronger partnerships with existing customers. Strong track record of hitting both operational goals and sales targets.

# **KEY SKILLS**

Customer obsessed mentality mindset. Strong relationship building skills based on sincerity and trust. Building rapport and providing concise communication to all levels within a customer's organization. Tenacity to meet targets with many examples of quick problem solving and thinking quickly on my feet.

## **EDUCATION**

Saint Mary's College of California 2016 - 2018 | Bachelors of Econonmics

# **EXPERIENCE**

## Sept 2019 -April 2020

#### YELP RESTAURANTS - SAN FRANCISCO

Account Executive/Restaurent Consultant

- Growing top line by building and developing relationships with Business Owners and Restaurant Groups.
- Continuously meeting sales targets. Chased deals and proactively pursued customer leads with high closure rate. Maintained strong post sales relationships to drive renewals.
- Using customer experiences and market research to drive ideas around marketing expansion and promotions to drive top line.

#### Sept 2018-Sept 2019

#### **PREVEDERE**

BDR Business (Development Representative)

- Leveraged: Cold Outreach and Linkedin Sales Navigator. Built targeted email campaigns, created one-pagers and infographics to help explain Predictive Analytics software capabilities.
- Sold SaaS Enterprise solution reaching out to the office of the CFO at Fortune 500 Companies, had to learn to work multiple channels to get the main decision maker.

#### May 2017 -Aug 2017

#### PLUG AND PLAY ACCELERATOR

Supply Chain and Logistic Vertical

- Worked closely with Corporate Partners to source Start-ups that solve industry-wide supply chain issues. Helped Corporate Partners with day to day needs when they would visit/work out of Plug and Play.
- Spearheaded: Research initiatives based on International Supply Chain and lead Intern projects.

### **JAN 2010**

### **UNDER THE BAOBOB TREE**

Part of a team of 10 students who planned and fundraised for a trip
to Malawi Africa, to teach local people about nutrition and crop
diversity. While building a garden for growing other crops besides
Corn.